

# JOSEFINE THEDEN-SCHOW FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER | BERLIN

osefine.thedenschow@gmail.com | +49 173 92 12 080 | https://github.com/jthedens | https://www.linkedin.com/in/josefine-theden-schov

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Le Wagon Berlin | Present

### Teaching Assistant

 Teaching core programming concepts and best practices to students, helping them understand complex technical challenges in order to find the most efficient way to solve them.

### Media Impact GmbH & Co. KG | Berlin | Jun 2016 - Sep 2019

Marketing Manager Mobile & Multiscreen - Digital Product Marketing

- Independent development of multiscreen products for an optimal monetization of the portfolio while acting as an interface to related departments, such as Sales, Brand Management and AdTechnology.
- Independent support and further development of external service providers as an additional monetization channel.

Frischepost GmbH | Hamburg | Jan - Apr 2016

Internship: Marketing & PR

Florian Schmitz Kommunikation GmbH | Hamburg | Oct - Dec 2015

Assistance to the CEO

Ligatus GmbH | Cologne | Dec 2014 - Jun 2015

Internship: International Business / Corporate Services

## WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

NightWatch http://www.night-watch.co/

A social network where users can recommend movies to each other and create personal watchlists: built with JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Ajax, HTML and CSS whilst also working as a team on Github/Heroku.

FamilyTime https://family-timeee.herokuapp.com/

AirBnB-style platform to book a family stay. App implemented searching and geocoding in Rails.

Mister Cocktail https://cocktailshaker.herokuapp.com/

## **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

# Le Wagon | Tel Aviv | Oct - Dec 2019

 9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

# Hochschule Fresenius University of Applied Science | Cologne | Sep 2011 - Aug 2014

Bachelor of Arts: Media and Communication Management

# Humanistisches Gymnasium Christianeum | Hamburg | Aug 2002 - Jun 2010

- General qualification for university entrance / A-levels
- Re-elected class representative (2002-2008)

# **ABOUT**

I am a 28-year-old experienced Marketing Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry, who wants to change her profession and work as a fullstack web developer.

I recently graduated from Le Wagon's 9-week fullstack coding bootcamp in Tel Aviv.

I build elegant, functional and user-friendly websites and web applications, and continue to improve my programming knowledge. I am currently learning React JS.

## **SKILLS**

- Ruby, Ruby On Rails, Html5, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap, Ajax, Heroku, Github, JavaScript, SQL, jQuery SQL, MVC Architecture
- MS Office
- SAP
- Salesforce

### **INTERESTS**

Art, Music, Innovation, Technology, Traveling, People, Cultures

J. Wellen Juan Berlin, 18.02.2020